{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954227420","data":{"timestamp":" 946954227420"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 3f73d3ad-72cc-462b-8fec-2b47446b2f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_244_244-900-450"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 244"," userResponse":" 244"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954305356","data":{"timestamp":" 946954305356"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 3f73d3ad-72cc-462b-8fec-2b47446b2f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_383_832-998-383"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 383"," userResponse":" 383"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954362476","data":{"timestamp":" 946954362476"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 3f73d3ad-72cc-462b-8fec-2b47446b2f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_414_885-512-414"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 414"," userResponse":" 414"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954444306","data":{"timestamp":" 946954444306"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 3f73d3ad-72cc-462b-8fec-2b47446b2f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_259_630-259-528"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 259"," userResponse":" 259"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954459604","data":{"timestamp":" 946954459604"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 3f73d3ad-72cc-462b-8fec-2b47446b2f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_112_461-128-112"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 112"," userResponse":" 112"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954710756","data":{"timestamp":" 946954710756"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 3f73d3ad-72cc-462b-8fec-2b47446b2f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_422_420-422-684"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 422"," userResponse":" 422"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954725412","data":{"timestamp":" 946954725412"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 3f73d3ad-72cc-462b-8fec-2b47446b2f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_272_272-699-619"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 272"," userResponse":" 272"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954753099","data":{"timestamp":" 946954753099"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 3f73d3ad-72cc-462b-8fec-2b47446b2f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_411_607-109-411"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 411"," userResponse":" 411"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954803754","data":{"timestamp":" 946954803754"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 3f73d3ad-72cc-462b-8fec-2b47446b2f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 74"," userResponse":" 74"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954819091","data":{"timestamp":" 946954819091"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 3f73d3ad-72cc-462b-8fec-2b47446b2f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_625_625-379-224"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 625"," userResponse":" 625"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954828541","data":{"timestamp":" 946954828540"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 3f73d3ad-72cc-462b-8fec-2b47446b2f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_625_625-379-224"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954837100","data":{"timestamp":" 946954837100"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 6e0fc90d-f4f4-4858-a86d-438704e098d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954837331","data":{"timestamp":" 946954837330"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 6e0fc90d-f4f4-4858-a86d-438704e098d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954838304","data":{"timestamp":" 946954838303"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 6e0fc90d-f4f4-4858-a86d-438704e098d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954839592","data":{"timestamp":" 946954839592"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 6e0fc90d-f4f4-4858-a86d-438704e098d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954842541","data":{"timestamp":" 946954842541"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 6e0fc90d-f4f4-4858-a86d-438704e098d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954843396","data":{"timestamp":" 946954843396"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 6e0fc90d-f4f4-4858-a86d-438704e098d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954843719","data":{"timestamp":" 946954843718"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 6e0fc90d-f4f4-4858-a86d-438704e098d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954844965","data":{"timestamp":" 946954844964"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 6e0fc90d-f4f4-4858-a86d-438704e098d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954848544","data":{"timestamp":" 946954848544"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 6e0fc90d-f4f4-4858-a86d-438704e098d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954849537","data":{"timestamp":" 946954849537"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 6e0fc90d-f4f4-4858-a86d-438704e098d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954849800","data":{"timestamp":" 946954849799"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 6e0fc90d-f4f4-4858-a86d-438704e098d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954850758","data":{"timestamp":" 946954850758"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 6e0fc90d-f4f4-4858-a86d-438704e098d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954853651","data":{"timestamp":" 946954853650"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 6e0fc90d-f4f4-4858-a86d-438704e098d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954854696","data":{"timestamp":" 946954854696"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 6e0fc90d-f4f4-4858-a86d-438704e098d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954855178","data":{"timestamp":" 946954855178"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 6e0fc90d-f4f4-4858-a86d-438704e098d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954859758","data":{"timestamp":" 946954859757"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 6e0fc90d-f4f4-4858-a86d-438704e098d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954859865","data":{"timestamp":" 946954859864"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 6e0fc90d-f4f4-4858-a86d-438704e098d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954934760","data":{"timestamp":" 946954934760"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 6e0fc90d-f4f4-4858-a86d-438704e098d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954946537","data":{"timestamp":" 946954946537"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 8b4be3c0-704c-416e-94bf-8cbe021d7f72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 74"," userResponse":" 74"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954965025","data":{"timestamp":" 946954965025"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 8b4be3c0-704c-416e-94bf-8cbe021d7f72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_272_272-699-619"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 272"," userResponse":" 272"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954993567","data":{"timestamp":" 946954993567"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 8b4be3c0-704c-416e-94bf-8cbe021d7f72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_112_461-128-112"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 112"," userResponse":" 112"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955118491","data":{"timestamp":" 946955118491"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 8b4be3c0-704c-416e-94bf-8cbe021d7f72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_244_244-900-450"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 244"," userResponse":" 244"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955172186","data":{"timestamp":" 946955172186"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 8b4be3c0-704c-416e-94bf-8cbe021d7f72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_411_607-109-411"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 411"," userResponse":" 411"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955215319","data":{"timestamp":" 946955215318"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 8b4be3c0-704c-416e-94bf-8cbe021d7f72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_259_630-259-528"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 259"," userResponse":" 259"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955299629","data":{"timestamp":" 946955299629"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 8b4be3c0-704c-416e-94bf-8cbe021d7f72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_383_832-998-383"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 383"," userResponse":" 383"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955315456","data":{"timestamp":" 946955315456"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 8b4be3c0-704c-416e-94bf-8cbe021d7f72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_625_625-379-224"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 625"," userResponse":" 625"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955340441","data":{"timestamp":" 946955340441"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 8b4be3c0-704c-416e-94bf-8cbe021d7f72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_422_420-422-684"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 422"," userResponse":" 422"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955357631","data":{"timestamp":" 946955357631"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 8b4be3c0-704c-416e-94bf-8cbe021d7f72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_414_885-512-414"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 414"," userResponse":" 414"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955364828","data":{"timestamp":" 946955364828"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 8b4be3c0-704c-416e-94bf-8cbe021d7f72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_414_885-512-414"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955369617","data":{"timestamp":" 946955369617"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 8b4be3c0-704c-416e-94bf-8cbe021d7f72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_414_885-512-414"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955376410","data":{"timestamp":" 946955376410"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 8b4be3c0-704c-416e-94bf-8cbe021d7f72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_414_885-512-414"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955381490","data":{"timestamp":" 946955381490"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" 8b4be3c0-704c-416e-94bf-8cbe021d7f72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_414_885-512-414"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955392718","data":{"timestamp":" 946955392718"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" e54133d9-d86c-4f55-ac5e-7ad5d8e48106"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_112_461-128-112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 112"," userResponse":" 112"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955516035","data":{"timestamp":" 946955516034"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" e54133d9-d86c-4f55-ac5e-7ad5d8e48106"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_414_885-512-414"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 414"," userResponse":" 414"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955526678","data":{"timestamp":" 946955526678"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" e54133d9-d86c-4f55-ac5e-7ad5d8e48106"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_259_630-259-528"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 259"," userResponse":" 259"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955547754","data":{"timestamp":" 946955547754"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" e54133d9-d86c-4f55-ac5e-7ad5d8e48106"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_625_625-379-224"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 625"," userResponse":" 224"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955562859","data":{"timestamp":" 946955562859"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" e54133d9-d86c-4f55-ac5e-7ad5d8e48106"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_625_625-379-224"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 625"," userResponse":" 625"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955577898","data":{"timestamp":" 946955577898"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" e54133d9-d86c-4f55-ac5e-7ad5d8e48106"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_422_420-422-684"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 422"," userResponse":" 422"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955629743","data":{"timestamp":" 946955629743"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" e54133d9-d86c-4f55-ac5e-7ad5d8e48106"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_244_244-900-450"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 244"," userResponse":" 244"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955685175","data":{"timestamp":" 946955685175"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" e54133d9-d86c-4f55-ac5e-7ad5d8e48106"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_272_272-699-619"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 272"," userResponse":" 272"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955737342","data":{"timestamp":" 946955737342"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" e54133d9-d86c-4f55-ac5e-7ad5d8e48106"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_383_832-998-383"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 383"," userResponse":" 383"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955766335","data":{"timestamp":" 946955766334"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" e54133d9-d86c-4f55-ac5e-7ad5d8e48106"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_411_607-109-411"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 411"," userResponse":" 411"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955812450","data":{"timestamp":" 946955812450"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" e54133d9-d86c-4f55-ac5e-7ad5d8e48106"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 74"," userResponse":" 74"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946955819918","data":{"timestamp":" 946955819917"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000104_054949"," gameId":" e54133d9-d86c-4f55-ac5e-7ad5d8e48106"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}